ltretire.com 2017-06-06

# FACTS

                                                                                                                    Rev. 01/2017
                         WHAT DOES LT Trust Company
   FACTS                 DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
   Why?                  Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                         consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                         how we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice
                         carefully to understand what we do.
   What?                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                         have with us. This information can include:
                                 Social Security number and account balance
                                 Account transactions and related transaction history
                                 Checking account and wire transfer instructions
                         When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this
                         notice.
   How?                  All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                         business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                         customers’ personal information; the reasons LT Trust Company chooses to share; and
                         whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                        Does LT Trust
    Reasons we can share your personal information                                              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                       Company share?
    For our everyday business purposes –
    such as to process your transactions, maintain
                                                                              Yes                             No
    your account(s), respond to court orders and legal
    investigations, or report to credit bureaus
    For our marketing purposes –
                                                                              No                       We don’t share
    to offer our products and services to you
    For joint marketing with other financial companies                        No                       We don’t share
    For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                                              Yes                             No
    information about your transactions and experiences
    For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                                              No                       We don’t share
    information about your creditworthiness
    For nonaffiliates to market to you                                        No                       We don’t share
  Questions?             Call 1-800-831-8675 or go to www.LTRetire.com
CRS-5560                                                                                                          #07INN104944

    Page 2
    Who we are
    Who is providing this notice?    LT Trust Company
    What we do
       How does LT Trust Company     To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
    protect my personal information? and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                     These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                     and buildings.
                                     Prospective employees are screened for criminal convictions and drug
                                     use. Once hired, employees are advised of LT Trust privacy policies.
       How does LT Trust Company     We collect your personal information, for example, when you
    collect my personal information?
                                             open an account or deposit money
                                             wire out or otherwise withdraw from your account
                                             direct us to buy or sell securities
                                     We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                     bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
    Why can’t I limit all sharing?   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                             sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information
                                              about your creditworthiness
                                             affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                             sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                     State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                     limit sharing.
    Definitions
    Affiliates                       Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                     financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                          •   LT Plan Services
                                          •   Plan Strategies Incorporated, a financial company
    Nonaffiliates                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                     financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                             LT Trust Company does not share with nonaffiliates so they
                                              can market to you.
    Joint marketing                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                     together market financial products or services to you.
                                             LT Trust Company does not jointly market.
CRS-5560                                                                                             #07INN104944
